Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/s-dov-lando (LinkedIn)

Top Skills
Hedge Funds
Private Equity
Alternative Investments

Dov Lando

General Counsel and Chief Compliance Officer at Crawford Lake Capital Management, LLC

Greater New York City Area

Summary

Experienced asset manager General Counsel and Chief Compliance Officer (GC / CCO), with leadership experience in global organizations.

Legal/compliance experience includes: launch and operation of liquid, illiquid, and hybrid investment vehicles, both registered and unregistered, operating under mandates including discretionary global macro, credit, multi-manager, portable alpha, real estate, and private equity; investor side letters; distribution arrangements; service contracts; marketing and investor relations; MNPI and insider trading controls; valuation; employment/HR matters; implementing and monitoring institutional quality global compliance programs for SEC and NFA registrants also regulated by the UK FSA (addressing the Investment Advisers Act of 1940, Investment Company Act of 1940, Securities Exchange Act of 1934, Securities Act of 1933, Employee Retirement Income Securities Act of 1974 (ERISA), and Commodity Exchange Act); mergers and acquisitions transactions; managing regulatory inquiries and audits; performing internal investigations; and litigation management.

Frequent speaker on alternative asset management legal, regulatory, and compliance matters, with a robust industry network.

Experience

Crawford Lake Capital Management, LLC General Counsel and Chief Compliance Officer August 2018 - Present

Lakewood, New Jersey

MKP Capital Management, L.L.C. General Counsel (and Chief Compliance Officer 2013-2016) April 2012 - April 2018 (6 years 1 month) Arden Asset Management LLC General Counsel May 2003 - April 2012 (9 years)

American International Group Assistant General Counsel September 2000 - May 2003 (2 years 9 months)

Schulte Roth & Zabel LLP
Associate
September 1995 - September 2000 (5 years 1 month)

Education

Fordham University School of Law JD · (1992 - 1995)

Yeshiva University
B.A., Economics · (1987 - 1991)